2daygeek.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy | 2daygeek.com

Our Privacy Policy governs your access to and use of the services, websites, and applications offered through 2DayGeek.

Please read this statement carefully before using or proceeding to access 2DayGeek site.

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy.

#### Non-personal identification information:

We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our Site.

Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider utilized and other similar information.

#### Web Browser Cookies:

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them.

User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

#### Information Security:

We work hard to protect 2DayGeek and our users from unauthorized access or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold.

In particular, we review the information collected including physical security to guard against unauthorized access to systems.

#### Google Adsense:

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet.

DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc.

You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy:

2DayGeek has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the information we collect.

You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

This document was last updated on **Nov 29, 2019**.
